<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>An act for constituting a committee for the army and treasurers at war</title>
            <author>England and Wales.</author>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1659</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 13 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 6 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2011-04">2011-04 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A37548</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing E1007A</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R32784</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">12754426</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">ocm 12754426</idno>
            <idno type="VID">93383</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A37548)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 93383)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 1526:13)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>An act for constituting a committee for the army and treasurers at war</title>
                  <author>England and Wales.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>8 [i.e. 10] p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>Printed by John Streater and John Macock ...,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1659.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>"Thursday, February 2, 1659. Ordered by the Parliament, that this act be forthwith printed and published. Thomas St. Nicholas, Clerk of the Parliament."</note>
                  <note>Pages 9-10 numbered 7-8.</note>
                  <note>Imperfect: print showthrough with slight loss of print.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>England and Wales. --  Army --  History.</term>
               <term>Finance --  Great Britain.</term>
               <term>Great Britain --  History --  Commonwealth and Protectorate, 1649-1660.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2009-06</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2009-07</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2009-09</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2009-09</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-04</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:93383:1"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 73 -->
            <pb facs="tcp:93383:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 73 -->
            <p>AN ACT For Conſtituting A COMMITTEE For the <hi>Army</hi> and <hi>Treaſurers</hi> at <hi>War.</hi>
            </p>
            <p>
               <floatingText xml:lang="eng">
                  <body>
                     <div type="license">
                        <opener>
                           <dateline>
                              <date>Thurſday <hi>February</hi> 2. 1659.</date>
                           </dateline>
                        </opener>
                        <p>
                           <hi>ORdered by the Parliament,</hi> That this Act be forth<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>with Printed and Publiſhed.</p>
                        <closer>
                           <signed>
                              <hi>THOMAS St. NICHOLAS</hi> Clerk of the Parliament.</signed>
                        </closer>
                     </div>
                  </body>
               </floatingText>
            </p>
            <figure>
               <figDesc>seal of the Commonwealth</figDesc>
            </figure>
            <p>
               <hi>LONDON,</hi> Printed by <hi>John Streater,</hi> and <hi>John Macock,</hi> Printers to the Parliament. 1659.</p>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="Act_of_Parliament">
            <pb facs="tcp:93383:2"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 74 -->
            <pb n="3" facs="tcp:93383:2" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 74 -->
            <head>AN ACT For Conſtituting A COMMITTEE For the ARMY And Treaſurers at War.</head>
            <p>FOr the more effectual and ſpeedy bringing in and orderly Mannagement, diſpoſing, and iſſuing forth of all Moneys that here<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tofore have beén, are, or before the tenth Day of <hi>October</hi> next enſuing ſhall be appointed for the uſe and payment of the Armies Garri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſons and Land-Forces of this Common-wealth and the incident Charges thereof.</p>
            <p>
               <pb n="4" facs="tcp:93383:3"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 75 -->
               <hi>Be it <unclear>Enacted</unclear>
               </hi> by this Preſent Parliament, And it is h<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>r<gap reason="illegible" extent="3 letters">
                  <desc>•••</desc>
               </gap> 
               <gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>nacted by the Authority thereof, That <hi>Tho. <gap reason="illegible" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap>
               </hi> elder <abbr>Eſq</abbr> Col. <hi>John Downes,</hi> Colonel <hi>Thomas <gap reason="illegible" extent="1+ letters">
                     <desc>•…</desc>
                  </gap>iſter, Edmond Weſt</hi> 
               <abbr>Eſq</abbr> 
               <hi>Rich<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ard Lucy</hi> 
               <abbr>Eſq</abbr> 
               <gap reason="illegible" extent="1 word">
                  <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
               </gap> 
               <hi>Anthony Samuel</hi> 
               <abbr>Eſq</abbr> or any three of them, ſhall be, and are hereby appointed and authorized to be a Committeé for the Army and Forces aforeſaid, and ſhall have full Power and are hereby Authorized to ſet down and give ſuch Order as they ſhall think fit and meét for the full Aſſeſsing, Re-aſſeſsing, Due Colle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cting, Leavying, and Payment of all and every the Sum and Sums of Money, that now are, heretofore have been, or within the time aforeſaid ſhall be Appointed, ſet apart, or Ordered, for the We and purpoſes before expreſſed: And ſuch Orders and Directions as ſhall be therein Given by the ſaid Committee, ſhall be Obſerved and O<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beyed by all and every the Commiſsioners, Aſſeſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſors, Collectors, Sub-Collectors, Receiver, and other Perſons whatſoever, that have been, are, or ſhall be Intruſted with, or Imployed in the Aſſeſsing, Leavying, Collecting, Receiving, or Payment of all or any part of the Moneys before-mentioned. And the ſaid Committee for the Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>my are hereby further Authorized and Impowred upon any neglect of Duty, abuſe of Truſt, or Complaint made of other Miſcariages of any Per<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſon or Perſons already Imployed or Concerned in the Apportioning, Aſſeſsing, Leavying, Col<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lecting, Receiving, or Payment of any part of the aforeſaid Moneys, to Hear and Examine, Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dreſs and Determine of and concerning the ſame, and aſwel therein, as in all matters of Difference that are, or ſhall happen to be, betweén any the Counties, Cities, Towns, or Places in <hi>England</hi>
               <pb n="5" facs="tcp:93383:3" rendition="simple:additions"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 75 -->and <hi>Wales,</hi> or betweén any the Hundreds, Divi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſions, Town-Ships, or Hamlets therein, to Or<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>der, Conclude, Adjudge, Execute, and do as they in their Diſcretion ſhall think fit; and to pu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>niſh all and every ſuch Perſon and Perſons as ſhall neglect or abuſe any Truſt Committed, or that ſhall be Committed to them in or concerning the Premiſes, be it by Fine or Impriſonment of the Parties offending, the Fine not exceeding Twenty Pounds, to be Imployed to the Vſe of the Army; and ſhall take care for the ſpeedy Execution of their Orders, Directions, and In<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtructions, by appointing of Forces or otherwiſe to cauſe Obedience thereunto.</p>
            <p>And <hi>Be it further Enacted by the Authority aforeſaid,</hi> That the ſaid Committee for the Army ſhall have Power, and are hereby Authorized by their Warrants, from time to time to Iſſue forth Aſsigne, and Diſpoſe of all and every ſuch ſum and ſums of Money aforeſaid, or any part there<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>of, as are or ſhall be due and payable to the For<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ces and Garriſons that are or ſhall be Imployed in the Service of this Commonwealth, accord<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing to their preſent allowance of Pay, or ſuch o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther allowance of Pay, Orders, or Eſtabliſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments as ſhall be Appointed by the Parliament, or Council of State, and alſo for the Payment and Satisfaction of ſuch Proviſions of Cloaths or Virtuals as ſhall be by Order of Parliament, or by the Council of State from time to time con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tracted for, and bought for the Vſe of the ſaid Forces and Garriſons, or other the Land-For<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ces of this Commonwealth, and for payment and ſatisfaction for ſuch Druggs and Medica<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments and other Neceſſaries, for any ſick or
<pb n="6" facs="tcp:93383:4"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 76 -->wounded Souldiers, whilſt they continue in the Army, as the ſaid Committee for the Army ſhall find Neceſſary to be bought and provided for the Vſe of all or any part of the afore<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſaid Forces, and for all other the Incident Charges of the Army and Forces aforeſaid, and other the purpoſes in this Act Expreſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſed.</p>
            <p>And the ſaid Committeé for the Army ſhall be and are hereby Authorized and Impowered from time to time to Order, Direct, and Appoint the tranſmitting and ſending ſuch ſum and ſums of money, as they ſhall from time to time find neceſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſary to be allowed and ſent into <hi>Ireland</hi> and <hi>Scot<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land</hi> for the uſe and payment of the Forces that are or ſhall be imployed in the Service of this Common-wealth, in either of the ſaid places, and to give their Orders to the Treaſurers at War hereafter in this Act named, their Deputy or Deputies for the payment of the ſaid Forces and Garriſons and Incident Charges thereof, out of the Moneys that ſhall be ſo tranſmitted and ſent to either of the ſaid places, according to ſuch Warrants as they ſhall receive in that be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>half from the Parliament, the Council of State, or Commiſſioners for the Army, according to their preſent allowance of pay, or ſuch other allow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ance of Pay or Eſtabliſhments as ſhall be here<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>after made by the Parliament or Council of State. And the ſaid Committeé for the Army ſhall be and are hereby impowered to Impreſſe, Take up, or Imploy ſuch Carriages by Land and ſuch Ships or Veſſels not being in the pay or ſervice of the Common-wealth, as they ſhall find neceſſary for the ſafe Carriage and Tranſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>porting
<pb n="7" facs="tcp:93383:4" rendition="simple:additions"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 76 -->of ſuch Treaſure as ſhall be by them appointed and aſſigned to be ſent into <hi>Ireland</hi> and <hi>Scotland,</hi> or to any other place for the uſe of any the Forces in the ſervice of this Common-wealth, and to pay for ſuch Carriages and Ships as they ſhall have occaſion to uſe for the purpoſes aforeſaid. And the ſaid Committeé for the Army ſhall be and are hereby Impow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ered and Authorized to Nominate, Appoint, and Imploy ſuch Clerks, Agents, Meſſengers and Servants, and to make and give unto them ſuch Sallaries, Allowances, and Satisfactions, as they ſhall think fit, having reſpect to the profit and advantage of the Common-wealth.</p>
            <p>And <hi>Be it further Enacted,</hi> And it is hereby Enacted by the Authority aforeſaid, That the ſaid Committeé for the Army ſhall in every Warrant granted by them, expreſſe for what pur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>poſe the Money contained in the ſame is to be iſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſued. And the Treaſurers at War hereafter in this Act named, and all other former Treaſu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rers at War are hereby enjoyned and required to obſerve ſuch Warrants or Orders as they ſhall receive from the Committeé for the Army, or any three of them for the purpoſes aforeſaid, the which ſaid Warrant or Warrants, together with the Receipt thereupon under the hand of the perſon or perſons to whom any ſum ſhall be directed to be paid; or his Aſſignee or Aſſignees, ſhall be to all and every the ſaid Treaſurers at War a ſufficient Diſcharge.</p>
            <p>And <hi>Be it Enacted,</hi> And it is hereby Enacted by the Authority aforeſaid, That <hi>James Nel<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thorpe</hi>
               <abbr>
                  <pb n="8" facs="tcp:93383:5"/>
                  <!-- PDF PAGE 77 -->Eſq</abbr> and <hi>John Lawſon</hi> 
               <abbr>Eſq</abbr> ſhall be, and are hereby appointed to be Receivers-General and Treaſurers at War for the Receiving, Pay<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing and Iſſuing forth of all Moneys that here<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tofore have beén, or before the tenth Day of <hi>Octo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ber, 1660.</hi> ſhall be appointed for the uſe and pay<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ment of the Forces aforeſaid, and Charges in<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cident thereunto. And the reſpective Receivers in the ſeveral Counties, that now are, hereto<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fore have been, or hereafter ſhall be appointed to receive any part of the Moneys herein before mentioned, ſhall forthwith after the Receipt there<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>of tranſmit and pay, or cauſe to be paid, the Mo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neys by them ſo received unto the ſaid Treaſurers at War, and Receivers-General herein before named, or where or to whom they ſhall appoint to Receive the ſame, and the Receipt of the ſaid Receivers-General and Treaſurers at War, ſhall be to the ſaid reſpective Receivers, and to all other Perſons, who ſhall by Vertue of this Act pay any Money unto them for the purpoſes aforeſaid, a ſufficient Diſcharge: And the ſaid Receivers-General and Treaſurers at War herein named, for their pains in Receiving, Pay<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing, and Iſſuing forth of all ſuch Moneys as ſhall be by Vertue of this Act Received by them, and Defraying the neceſſary Charges and Ex<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pences they ſhall be put unto in the doing there<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>of; And in conſideration that they ſhall exe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cute the Imployment of Treaſurers at War, until the Tenth Day of <hi>October,</hi> One Thouſand ſix hundred ſixty, ſhall have and receive after the rate of four and twenty hundred pounds by the Year, together with ſuch extraordinary Charges as ſhall be occaſioned by the Portage, or
<pb n="7" facs="tcp:93383:5" rendition="simple:additions"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 77 -->tranſporting of Monyes by Land or Sea, which the ſaid Committee for the Army, or any three of them, are hereby authorized and appointed by their order to allow unto them, from time to time, as they ſhall think fit. And Be it further Enacted and Declared by the Authority aforeſaid, That the Committee or Commiſsioners for the Army, for the time be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing, or any three or more of them, do at or be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fory the end of one whole year now next enſu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing, and from thenceforth yearly once every year, call to accompt the ſaid Treaſurers at Warr, or the Heires, Executors, or Admini<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtrators of them, or ſuch of them as ſhall be deceaſed (if any ſhall happen ſo to be) for all the Monyes which ſhall be by them received, either as Receivors-Generall of the Aſſeſs<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>me<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>ts, or Treaſurers at Warr out of the Aſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſeſsments, or by any other wayes or meanes, ſaving and excepting ſuch Monyes as ſhal be by them received at the Receipt of the publick Exchequer, and to give unto them, ingroſſed in Parchment under their hands, a Diſcharge for ſo much of the ſaid Monyes as ſhall be by them duely and juſtly accompted for. And it is likewiſe Enacted and Declared, That the firſt and ſecond Remembrancers of the publick Exchequer, upon tender unto them of ſuch Diſcharge as aforeſaid, ſhall record and inroll the ſame in the reſpective Offices, which being ſo Recorded and Inrolled, or the In<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rolment or Exemplification thereof ſhall be unto the ſaid Treaſurers at War, their heirs, Executors, and Adminiſtrators, and their and every of their Eſtates reall and perſonall, a good, valid, and ſufficient Diſcharge to all in<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tents
<pb n="8" facs="tcp:93383:6"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 78 -->and purpoſes whatſoever, without any other or further Accompt to be rendred or made for the ſaid Monyes, ſo accompted for as aforeſaid, or any part thereof.</p>
            <p>And it is further Enacted and Declared by the A<gap reason="illegible: missing" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>thority aforeſaid, That the ſaid Trea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſurers at <gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>arr, their Heirs, Executors, and Adminiſtrators, do and ſhall, when they ſhall be thereunto required by the ſaid Committee or Commiſsioners for the Army, or any three or more of them, within ſuch time, and accor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ding to ſuch Rules, as ſhall be appointed, di<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>recte, or given in that behalf by the ſaid Co<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>
               <g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mittee or Commiſsioners, or any three or more of them, paſs &amp; perfect their Accompts for the Monyes ſo to be accompted for as a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>foreſaid, and every part and parcell thereof.</p>
            <p>And Be it Enacted, and it is hereby further Enaeted, That <hi>John Blackwel</hi> and <hi>Richard Dean</hi> Eſquires, late Treaſurers at War, ſhall forthwith pay unto the preſent Treaſurers at Warr by this Act conſtituted, all and every ſum and ſums of Mony remaining in their hands as Treaſurers at Warr, and do hence<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>forth forbear, and are hereby diſcharged, to receive or diſpoſe of any Monyes, any way aſsigned for the Armies and Forces of this Common-wealth.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="license">
            <opener>
               <dateline>
                  <date>Thurſday, <hi>February</hi> 2. 1659.</date>
               </dateline>
            </opener>
            <p>ORdered by the Parliament, That this Act be forthwith Printed and Publiſhed.</p>
            <closer>
               <signed>
                  <hi>THOMAS St. NICHOLAS,</hi> Clerk of the Parliament.</signed>
            </closer>
            <pb facs="tcp:93383:6" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 78 -->
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
